

# **Tyler Angell**



### **Summary**

Self-taught web developer since 2019 while working full-time as an RF Electrical Engineer II. Experience as product owner/lead and working with large codebases, research, and Agile CCA build environment. Looking for a developer role to build upon current programming experience and problem-solving skills.

#### **Work Experience**

#### **Full Stack Web Developer**

Jan 2022 – Present

#### **Self-employed/Freelance** | Phoenix, AZ

- ▶ Developed websites using Next.JS (React with SSR).
- ▶ Built E-Commerce website: Redux Toolkit for shopping cart, PayPal Standard Checkout, and PostgreSQL.
- ▶ Designed wireframes for websites using Figma.
- ▶ Drafted requirements from client consultations.

# **RF Electrcial Engineer II**

June 2018 – Jan 2022

#### Raytheon | Tucson, AZ

- ▶ Used Python with PyVisa to automate test equipment and evaluate ADC/DAC.
- ▶ Updated legacy codebase in MATLAB for new hardware.
- ▶ Designed and wrote testing automation scripts in LabVIEW.
- ▶ Wrote VBA script to find discrepancies in EDM (Raytheon parts list) data.

# **RF Engineering Intern**

Aug 2017 - April 2018

## General Dynamics | Scottsdale, AZ

- ▶ Bread boarding RF components for failure analysis and characterization.
- ▶ Used HFSS to design and simulate divider, coupler, filter, and connector transitions.

#### **Education**

Master of Science in Engineering, Electrical Engineering	May 2018
Bachelor of Science in Engineering, Electrical Engineering	May 2017
Arizona State University at Barrett, the Honors College   Tempe, Arizona	<b>GPA: 3.95</b>

#### **Relevant Coursework**

♦ Python for Engineers	♦ Numerical Methods using MATLAB
♦ Data Mining & Machine Learning	♦ C++, Intro to Programming
♦ UX/UI Design	♦ Hardware Design Language Programming Logic (VHDL)

#### **Projects**

# Time-Series Forecasting using LSTM Networks and Prophet

*Python for Engineers – Final Deliverable* (<a href="https://tangellaz.github.io/LSTM-vs-Prophet/">https://tangellaz.github.io/LSTM-vs-Prophet/</a>)

- ▶ Used python and machine learning to compare forecasting algorithms: LSTM & Prophet.
- ▶ Developed novel method for LSTM model to predict upon its previous predicted value (forecast).

#### Simulating Effects of Probe Placement on Calibration Accuracy using TRL

Millimeter Wave & THz Measurements – Final Deliverable (<a href="https://tangellaz.github.io/THz-project/">https://tangellaz.github.io/THz-project/</a>)

- ▶ Used HFSS to model calibration standards for thru, reflect, load (TRL).
- ▶ Used Python to introduce error (Gaussian noise) simulating probe placement error and plot results.
- ▶ Successfully showed percent error increases exponentially as a function of probe displacement.

#### RFID Lock using MSP4332P401R and TRF7970A Booster Pack

Texas Instruments Internship Design Challenge

- ▶ Used C++ to develop state machine for RFID Lock.
- ▶ Discovered bug in TI firmware release and showed failure mode in RFID reader.

#### **Ultra-Smart-Brain Full Stack Web App**

*Udemy Web Development Course Project* 

- ▶ Used React and Redux to make face recognition application using Clarifai's API.
- ► Created a database using PostgreSQL to store user information and stats.

#### **Professional Skills**

♦ React, Next.JS	♦ Figma	♦ GitHub	♦ C++, MATLAB
♦ JavaScript, TypeScript	♦ PostgreSQL	♦ Python	♦ LabVIEW
♦ HTML, CSS	♦ HTTP Methods	♦ Machine Learning	♦ HW Test & Automation